

PHÙNG VĂN VIỆT Frontend Developer

- (iii) Aug 17, 1994
- Male
- 0706149044
- vanvietdct@gmail.com
- 🛪 Danang, Vietnam
- 🗞 https://fuvavi.com

SKILLS

REACTJS

VUEJS

TYPESCRIPT

HTML5 & CSS3

HIML5 & C553

JAVASCRIPT

GIT

WORDPRESS

PHOTOSHOP/FIGMA/XD

SEO

SOFT SKILLS

ABOUT ME

Web Developer specializing in frontend development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, MySQL. Experienced in using Photoshop, XD and Figma to design website interfaces.

Outside of work, I also have a hobby of blogging and Fuvavi.com is my personal blog.

EDUCATION

SEP 2012 - MAY 2015

DA NANG TECHNOLOGY COLLEGE | Major: Information Technology

Ranking: Good

JUN 2016 - AUG 2016

PHP PROGRAMMING CERTIFICATE - IVIETTECH | Major: PHP Programming

Ranking: Good

WORK EXPERIENCE

JULY 2022 - PRESENT

OLMO TECHNOLOGY | Frontend Developer

- · Product development for the company's business
- Good knowledge of TypeScript, JavaScript, jQuery, Vuejs, Reactjs, and pre-processing languages such as LESS/SASS/SCSS.
- · Skilled in source code management with Git.
- Experienced in SEO standard website design.

JUL 2017 - JULY 2022

BAP IT CO., JSC | Frontend Developer

- Good knowledge of layout techniques and frameworks such as Bootstrap, Material, and Ant Design.
- Good knowledge of HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Vuejs, Reactjs, and pre-processing languages such as LESS/SASS/SCSS.
- Good knowledge of web service development (REST), security, and performance for web applications.
- Skilled in source code management with Git.
- Develop the company's website on WordPress CMS.
- Experienced in SEO standard website design.
- Participate in project development for customers.
- Company product development combining Vuejs and WordPress.
- Training HTML/CSS for interns.

JUN 2016 - JUL 2017

BAP IT CO., JSC | Joomla Developer

- Develop the company's website on Joomla CMS.
- Design landing page for Customers.

HIGHLIGHT PROJECTS

TRACNGHIEM.VN

ONLINE MULTIPLE CHOICE EXAM SYSTEM.

DESIGNED BY FIGMA. FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT WITH VUEJS.

Team work

Problem Solving skill

Time management

Analytical skill Seft study skill

KEPLERAPP.VN

KEPLER - SOCIAL E-COMMERCE PLATFORM FOR WELLNESS. FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT WITH REACTJS

MKT.RAKUZA.IO

NFT MAKET PLACE - FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT WITH REACTJS.

FUVAVI.COM

PERSONAL PROJECTS: A BLOG DEVELOPED ON WORDPRESS CMS PLATFORM DESIGNED WITH SEO STANDARDS

COMMUNITY

DEVELOPMENT A FACEBOOK GROUP COMMUNITY FOR IT ENGINEERS WITH 27K MEMBERS - FRONT END DEVELOPER VIET NAM

CERTIFICATIONS

2022

HAS SUCCESSFULLY REACHED THE TOP 20% OF CANDIDATES PASSING THE SKILL OF HTML - TOP CV

2022

HAS SUCCESSFULLY REACHED THE TOP 20% OF CANDIDATES **PASSING THE SKILL OF JAVASCRIPT - TOP CV**

2022

CERTIFICATE OF PARTICIPATION - ATEN ENGLISH SCHOOL